This is a lot but general insurance company has
taken over Indian General Insurance Company after take off and some of their
products have come in handy,
they have relaunched them according to their own choice,
so today I will
request those products, one of them is the product I will
talk about Bad Health Advantage 100, before starting with you,
my name is Prince Koun Tips Ko and I
am Saffron Chun,
elastic 0 set from the insurance industry and in this way I bring these
videos so that your
personal life becomes easy and simple five ways and
elephants because our side
is creating awareness of not let's go through the
video, Ubar Health Advantage is a
new product launched, this product is a
product of Isar Robot, earlier it used to be in Indian
times, this product has been relaunched by
changing some features according to their choice, in
which there are three variants Prime
Gaur and Fikr, so these teams have
divided the variants accordingly, first let's talk about the
main eligibility features,
quality, its entries quality near
maximum entry  Justified this year's
entries 90 maximum entries 2012 and life
gravity is the Kundali Bhagya of the policy
after the child will have to take a different quality polish
plate will be individual powers where
available house of this water policy
is available in front total there is combination to dance plus
4 maximum plus to 13 inch plus to
front and loss to turn on people
can come in a single policy will talk about room
in room gelatin room rent that in prime there is
room rent one per cent of Sameshwar
maximum and 2% if you are not aware
oil app there is no typing in it time and
which
is available in mez two three and four lions and royal from 5 lakh to 15 lakh
option is available in effect from seventh
class to Sikar road so you can choose which plan as per your choice
after seeing these benefits
so this hospitalization
is prevent hospitalization before going to hospital
expenses and talk during
your sleep related to lord
Hospitalization popular hospitalization
is Prime Minister TDS
from post hydration is my the royal and
significance of husband hospitalization is
postman's date in various AYUSH benefits in
you the hospitalization of Kavad AYUSH
in all three including Kanwar pilgrims there is
ward AYUSH Ayurvedic, Unani, Siddha
and Homeopathy so there is a
definition for AYUSH treatment that
where can you take AYUSH hospitalization and
what facilities should be there where you are getting AYUSH treatment let me
tell you something also so
one thing is that there should be a comment the
hospital which is AYUSH hospital only AYUSH
activity should be there the complete
data should be maintained we should maintain it on whoever
comes near the space station the
classification should be white the
person who is in the hospital
will qualify in AYUSH if we talk about it clearly then there
is a list of 586 looking at it
organ donor is there but this is not road
ambulance 1% you understand and maximum cases
of animal biotechnology are there now  We will talk about ₹10
kilometer payment and its
benefits on various SIM is aarambh
and fiction
half up to Sameshwar on in English hum and
different illnesses
for this you can plan side
related canal related play is the
concept of guaranteed balance and you will also come to know why it is guaranteed,
basically if you do not take no claim bonus then
see the incentive to the companies, your time gets
increased, if you use the car for half an hour then it
means the no claim bonus that will be
given to you will be guaranteed and
Lifestyle means once you pay it then
you will get 20%, at the
end of the semester suppose you did not make any claim for your 10 lakh time then
you get 20% no claim
bonus, today's 20%
students will see that your problem will be solved,
if you take 12th year then the
two lines that you have got will not be there but
you will not get no claim bonus for that year, you have already
given approval which will remain in track,
means once  You get such a direction of 10 lakhs,
a different will go, this last one is
great, fry it for a minute, then if it reduces then the
policy of 20 lakhs will run for life time,
such cups are available, cups of sugar have been taken, those
above 18 years of age and those who are above 18 years can
take it in the policy, then that point
five percent of it is always and the maximum limit is
tent house, total absence of chakli, you can do whatever you
get in the tweet, in the voting which is
done at home, the toss button is in front of you,
Shahriyar Pisaach is near, there is no comment in the creature, it is
converted into roulette act, which is your
weight control surgery, dress power and
in this you can always take 50%,
whatever your Ramesh Yadav's fifty percent
maximum ₹1000000 here, both the oily
tablets, so there are some conditions for this, I am
your 3 year meeting, after the batting year,
this rock, it should be above the torn-torn in your wife,
then you can take it or
if it is above thirty five, then your  She is a wife and her
body is due to medical consumption, the doctor said and there are
many commodities due to which
bariatric surgery is mandatory, it is
medically necessary, so you will get the film right now,
Max Clixense benefits in which
if you are limited to 10 inches above 10 inches in the hospital,
then the company will give you this
alarm benefit which is Rs 20,000
in all three appearances and this word was always
and is done here, all these in-will
benefits which are already inbuilt in Glance,
now we will talk about what optional benefits you
can avail, which
you can use as per your convenience by paying additional premium,
if you have any requirement then we are going to
tell you some in the manifesto, it
is not covered in Pride, there is a road block, there is
maternity benefit, you can mute it back,
but it is okay, a good benefit has been given
because maternity is a word after ninth in it,
but there are some permissions, so in this
your page would have been  If it is two to three or
till delivery then you can take ten percent of your
shoulder but maximum ₹10
and of maternity benefit is included in fuel
proportionately which is felt
before the baby is born, there is an
increase in the chapter, there are consultations, even
later it is called post natal,
those are the patients who come out, there is a discount there only, so you will
not get it separately, its oil amount will be NIT
Central staff7 Mishra or
maximum ₹10 will be given, like I
met in this, there is a waiting period for salt in it,
maternity is covered only after ninth
but you will have to pay a premium of 3 years,
if you do the love apprenticeship of the pimples
then you can take normal pada maternity
benefit, so it is a very good option
because many times it happens that people
get the benefits as soon as possible, so there is
usually a minimum
waiting period of two years in it, so whatever maternity benefit you give in cheese  There is a
button in it but they are taking the paper of three years from you
and along with this she was saying that if Mali does
not plan the maternity benefit after his seniors then whatever maternity premium you will have to pay for the next day,
that too will be added as the first part of the maternity benefit and will
take it from you there only. I started thinking early in the morning that I am
making a video in which I will talk about
different types of immortality plants
and I will share the most successful event with you, that will be available
soon on our channel, so stay tuned, let's move
ahead and in optional benefits, like
we talked about maternity benefit, along with this
you can also take the cover for new born baby, the
cover for new born baby is Agyeya said that
if your net is automatically simple in the net
then you will take it, you can take which trials
of tiffin fatality benefits, suppose
you have taken Vitamin D for one week then you can change the
hospitalization benefit for new born baby for two lakhs,
now the definition
of vaccination for new born baby is as
you know  That you get this
money for vaccination and in the first year you
can always take a cent off on this decision,
you will get maximum cases, you will
not get more than that and this will be available for one year, this is full
youth, you can see extreme by doing this optional rider,
next Radhe-Radhe Gyan
Price, there is no constipation in this Georgette, there
is news of sex and minimum, now
Sameshwar you can take OPD benefit
is available, which is medical and dental benefit,
its designer is point five percent
of mixed maximum light switches on
Tuesday, this is your benefit
stitch less, that means here is their network
list, you can apply wherever you have time,
now you will get it done, you
cannot do this for pimples, Somesh Solitaire Plus
only, you
can cut in the next purpose lieutenant cover in this,
portion accidental death guest department
for disability and I have
also included obscene disability and the maximum
is not above 250 lakh per lakh and if you
want to invest on vitamins, you can also add this
Optional Title Now we will talk about the
waiting period in bathing rope polish. It is
important to know that, so let's see the waiting list below
which is in every polythene. So the mark on this list is a
waiting ticket that you
cannot get a plane hospitalization done for some time,
accidental emergency travel from day one in
all the plants are cyclone turmeric plants. Then we will
talk about specific users juice people -
it is 1718 NSS, if there is news then it will be done for a
year, then this noodles, here
in two years, that in many other
policies there is a waiting period of 30 years,
but here it is done only after two years,
so they don't want this, you can see for you those who
want that at least the bathing
roots are on pre-existing, then we will talk about this plant
photo, in this year the co-payment
is optional co-payment, that means suppose
if you want to reduce the volume then there is no
problem in it, but if you
want to increase your cream end use then you
can choose a co-payment of near 20%, your
premium will be reduced now both your
wires  If it remains then 30 days on son to and
secondly the zone is basically yours
Delhi-NCR Kolkata-Mumbai intruding
rubble local Pune and Hyderabad all cities in the
states of Gujarat Haryana and
Rajasthan this is the estimate here there will be
no discount on applying full premium pack
and no Manna Dey will be there only no one
can do it in any kind of President zone without any payment to anyone first is
India second is don't u all state
capitals which were in duty zone
except them all the artist of pistol will
come in want to here you
get discount on premiere of Salman's film on that
there is 12.5% ​​less premium and the same is the
payment to Swiss roll understand the discount you are getting the
company is
giving you a discount of 12.5% ​​on the program
201 premium and the same is the payment to you
if you get Jainul treatment done Sonu
Mishra there is no problem if the minister will do it there is no
problem if both are
done together then 12.5% ​​you will have to share the payment
in the bill 12.5% ​​of the
remaining zones  If you are not coming in, there are
two ways, so here you get 50%
discount from normal but there is a payment of 14%.
If you bring Jaunpuriya Jungle, then
if you bring Long then there is a
payment of 12.5%. If both of you
live together then you will have to pay a payment of 50%. There are
option rides and liters
which you can take, like if there is a
decline in the letter then in critical illness insurance, there
is a 2013-th butt which you get a loan som benefit,
one week critical
hospitalization is invested in your policy,
that is the butt which you will discuss with yourself, if you
want to take option benefit on that, then if the owner knows the
credit balance of all his/her family then an
alarm will be generated, they will have to take care of the
spices, that is, you have to survive for a minimum of 30 days,
after 3902 there
is a special, if someone crosses then you
get the benefit of maintenance, I will talk to you, please discuss the
premium, talk to me about the problem  We
will do the plan of looking for a family floater plan
and there is a two part plus two and
tippan, I have taken Monday's
premium and the novel we are discussing is the swelling
of PM train live status two to 8 9 6
included tasty 18 per cent IS installed
so there is a cream of two to 16 and this
will be baked and all the benefits 24 that we talked about will be
available to you in your policy you can ask any
health advantage long than bow tie if you have
any question you can
ask anything regarding this plan if you want to
donate something then you know our
first number and email ID is mentioned in it
please tell me
how to make the next video or and
you can get in touch with that in case of any query
and ask reminder if
you have not subscribed to my channel yet then
please do subscribe
and I had said that by Diwali there should be
10,000 more subscribers on this channel
so inch and you will complete the support and
I  I promise I wo
n't clean it up for you I'll give you the LED light information it right on
time and thank you so much hey
quickly cover it with a rickshaw
[Music]